milesplit.us 2011-06-05

# Privacy Policy - MileSplit United States

Updated: October 18, 2007 

MileSplit, Inc. will always look after the best interests and the privacy of our visitors first. This Site is offered and made available only to users 13 years of age or older who reside in the United States of America, its territories and possessions ("U.S."). If you are not yet 13 years old, or do not reside in the U.S., please discontinue using the Site immediately, or if, for any reason, you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the features, activities and services that require you to provide your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy is legally binding on all users. 

**What information do you collect about me?**  
MileSplit collects personal identifying information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us on website and through email. When visiting our online sites, we collect volunteered information such as survey information and/or site registration. 

**What's in it for me?**  
Plenty! The information we collect allows us to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each visitor. Plus, it enables us to notify you about updates to our Web site...contact you with special offers of interest...and customize your Web site experience. In addition, information is shared with reputable organizations who may contact you with special offers of possible interest. 

**What are "cookies" and what do they do for me?**  
Cookies are a small file that your web browser stores in order for a web site to store a bit of information that it can retrieve later. A web site can only read cookie data that it wrote and not cookies that other web sites set. We use cookies to allow you to login, remember your preferences, and other such things. 

**With whom do you share information about me?**  
We will not share your information with third parties unless you authorize it. For example, you may choose to allow us to share your information with Rodale Inc., the publisher of Runner's World and Running Times Magazines. The only other exception would be where we are legally required to do so or in order to protect public safety. We will never sell or otherwise provide your information to a third party without your permission. 

**Links**  
Our site may, on occasion, contain links to other sites with information gathering practices different from our own. Visitors should consult privacy policies for all other sites as we have no control over information submitted to or collected by such third parties. 

Our site sometimes offers promotions sponsored or co-sponsored by third parties. These third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. We have no control over the third party sponsor's use of this information. This site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third party sponsors will be provided access to such information. 

**What if I don't want e-mail from MileSplit?**  
We do not send out an regular emails or bulk mails. But if you want to be excluded from any communication with us, please let us know by emailing admin@milesplit.com. 

**May I see the information you collect about me?**  
Yes! Upon request, we provide our customers with access to personal account information and contact information. You may access the information by logging in to your account (if you created one) and change your information or settings at any time. Just login and then click on the "Profile" link at the top right of any page. From your profile there will be edit buttons that allow you to make changes to different areas. You will not be able to change your login name or email address. This is because both of these must be unique in our system and also because we require valid email addresses. 

**Changes...**  
We may need to change this privacy policy from time to time in order to address new issues, evolving technologies, changes on our sites or business practices. We may change this policy without notice to you but we will post those changes so you will always know what information we gather and how we might use that information. Please refer back to this policy regularly. 

**Rules for Submissions and Messages**  
Responsibility for what is posted in the discussion forums lies with each user--you alone are responsible for the content of your messages, and the consequences of any such messages. We cannot and do not review every submission a user may make. We neither endorse nor guarantee the accuracy or propriety of any submission. We do, however, reserve the right but do not assume the obligation to restrict or prohibit your use of our sites if we believe you are violating any of the terms of the agreement and to remove, edit, or relocate any submission as we see fit whether for legal or other reasons. 

**Member Conduct**  
You understand that all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that you, and not MileSplit, Inc., are entirely responsible for all Content that you upload, post or otherwise transmit. We do not control the Content posted and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. You understand that by using the site, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable. 

**You agree to not use our site in order to:**  
upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable; harm minors in any way; impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, a MileSplit official, forum leader, guide or host, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity; forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any Content transmitted through the Service or develop restricted or password-only access pages, or hidden pages or images (those not linked to from another accessible page); upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that you do not have a right to transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements); upload, post or otherwise transmit any Content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party; upload, post or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation, except in those areas of the Service that are designated for such purpose; upload, post or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; interfere with or disrupt the servers or networks connected to the site, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the site; intentionally or unintentionally violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, including, but not limited to, regulations promulgated by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, any rules of any national or other securities exchange, including, without limitation, the New York Stock Exchange, the American Stock Exchange or the NASDAQ, and any regulations having the force of law; "stalk" or otherwise harass another; collect or store personal data about other users; promote or provide instructional information about illegal activities, promote physical harm or injury against any group or individual, or promote any act of cruelty to animals. use your home page (or directory) as storage for remote loading or as a door or signpost to another home page engage in commercial activities without the express written consent of MileSplit, Inc. This includes, but is not limited to, the following activities: offering for sale any products or services; soliciting for advertisers or sponsors; conducting raffles or contests that require any type of entry fee; displaying a sponsorship banner of any kind, including those that are generated by banner or link exchange services displaying banners for services that provide cash or cash-equivalent prizes to users in exchange for hyperlinks to their web sites. 

**Rights**  
You acknowledge that we acquire all Rights to use any posted materials as described above so that we do not violate any Rights you may have in materials you post. By submitting content to or through our sites, you grant us the non-exclusive right to reproduce, modify and distribute it as we see fit in any medium and for any purpose in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed. You also permit any other user to access, display, and print such content for personal use. You vouch that any material you submit does not violate, plagiarize or infringe upon the right of any third party, including copyright, trademark or proprietary rights. If non-original content is included in your posting, you must obtain permission from the content owner and attribute it. 

**We appreciate the opportunity to serve you!**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy statement or if you feel that this site has not followed its stated information policy, feel free to contact us. Our postal address is: 1035 Pine Street, Apopka, FL 32703 and we can be reached via e-mail at: admin@milesplit.com. 

**Why should you trust us?**  
Because we're good people! And we hate spam email just as much as you do! 

**How will we secure your credit card/financial information?**  
We do not store any credit card or other financial data.
